Ouryou Rouichi
Mr. Ouryou, your daughter is here to see you again.
王陵さん　また娘さんがお見舞いに来てくださったわよ
Isn't that nice?
よかったですね
I'm sorry, but your father knows
you're here and is happy to see you too.
ごめんなさいね
お父さんもちゃんと分かってて 喜んでくださってますから
Please don't get discouraged.
気を落とさないでくださいね
Yes, of course.
ええ　もちろん
That's a lie. Everyone here is the same.
嘘だ　ここにいる人々の全てがそうだ
They don't notice anything. They don't say anything.
何も気付かず 何も語らず そして何も考えない
They don't think anything.
They are mere shells of their former selves,
ただの抜け殻のように生きて やがて
soon to disappear like the melting snow.
雪が解けるように消えていく
This epidemic leads innocent people to their deaths,
罪なき人々を死に至らしめる伝染病
and yet, its pathogen will never be eradicated.
でも　この病原菌が根絶されることはない
This is the disease called serenity,
これは安らぎという名の病
a form of death that people have wished for.
人々が望んだ死の形
Dare ni mo miserarenai mono
My head is full of things
Atama no naka afurete
That I can never tell anybody of
In this perfect world
Machigai sae mo nai sekai he
I roam, a lost being
Mayoikonderu
Arienai hodo surikomareteru
This world is impossibly hard on me
It's an illusion that plays out before my eyes
Me ni mieru mono dake no "sekai" genshou
Abakidaseru kana
Can I find its faults?
Plastic tac tic
Plastic, all is plastic
Mou dare mo okashiku narenai yo
Nobody is allowed to be insane
Kisama mo plastic beautiful world
You're made of plastic too, like this beautiful world
In this beautiful world
Utsukushi sugiru sekai ni
Boku wa nazeka
There is something
Hikari ga mienakute
That obscures all light for me
Haretsu shite yuku kokoro ga
My heart tries to break out
And finds no answer
Mugen no rifurekushon
Secret kills for you
Secret remains for you
The secret remains for you
Don't show me a dark future
Misekake no iro to
Mirai wo abakanai de
Nor a world of pretense
Keep it secret motion
Keep our motion secret
#07: Symbolism of Bletilla Striata
本字幕由诸神字幕组制作 更多字幕欢迎访问http://www.kamigami.org
翻译:草泥马 TMR@10 校对:西西   后期:时末
This is...
Don't tell me...
They first dismembered and cut open the body,
これって… まさか…
and then they used plastination to turn it into a human specimen.
Then they brought it right into
the middle of town and displayed it...
バラバラに切り開いた遺体をプラスティネーションで標本にして
I'm taking you off this case, Kougami.
そいつを街のど真ん中に飾りつけてくれたわけよ
What?
Why... Gino?
今回の捜査から外れてもらうぞ　狡噛
I can't allow a detective who can't put aside his preconceived notions
to be a part of the initial investigation.
何でだ　ギノ
Even so...
余計な先入観にとらわれた刑事を初動捜査に加えるわけにはいかない
そんな…でもまだ標本事件と一緒ってわけじゃ…
We still don't know if this is connected to the Specimen Case.
Ah!
So I'm on standby at my quarters, right?
宿舎で待機だな
That's right.
そうだ
Inspector Tsunemori.
常守監視官
Y-Yes!
はっ　はい
It seems that you're aware of the circumstances.
どうやら事情は知っている様子だし
Watch Kougami at all times and
make sure he doesn't do anything stupid.
狡噛が妙なことをしでかさないよう 付きっきりで監視しろ
That'll be your job during this case.
それが今回の 君の仕事だ
I'll summarize the case.
整理する
The dismembered body found in
a park in Daikanyama, Shibuya ward
渋谷区代官山の公園で発見されたバラバラ死体は
belonged to Kuzuhara Satsuki,
葛原沙月
who was a student at Ousou Academy, a private college for girls.
全寮制の女子高等教育機関桜霜学園の生徒だ
She went missing a week ago.
１週間前から行方不明になっていた
Hey, Ousou Academy is...
おい　「桜霜学園」って
...where Touma Kouzaburo,
the suspect in the Specimen Case, worked.
標本事件の容疑者 藤間幸三郎の勤務先
Right?
でしたよね
The body was eroded by a special kind of chemical,
遺体は特殊な薬剤に浸食され タンパク質がプラスチック状に変質
and the protein was converted into plastic form.
Analysis confirmed that the chemical used
was the same one used in the case three years ago.
分析の結果　これは３年前の事件で使われた薬品と同一であることが判明した
It's more than likely that these cases share the same culprit.
確かに同一犯の可能性は高い
So after three years, the mysterious killer returns, huh?
謎の殺人鬼が３年ぶりにカムバックってわけか
Gino! Was it really okay to take Ko off the case?
ギノさーん ホントにコウちゃん 外してよかったんすか
He's been investigating the Specimen Case all this time, right?
あの人標本事件の調査って続行してたでしょ
He might've been able to find us some new leads.
何か新しい手掛かりとかつかんでたかも
I've read his report.
やつの報告書には目を通してある
It's completely delusional.
あれは　ただの妄想の羅列だ
You're going too far!
やり過ぎですよ 狡噛さん
Kougami.
Whoa!
You've got the sparring program on the highest difficulty level!
スパーリング最高レベルに設定してあるじゃないですか
Are you really human, Kougami?
本当に人間ですか　狡噛さん
Yeah.
ああ　それでもパラライザーで撃たれれば気絶する
I mean, all it takes is one Paralyzer and I'm out like a light.
I'm just your average, weak human.
ただのやわな人間だ
I bet the Property Management Division's gonna give you hell for this.
後で絶対に管財課から怒られますよ
Not my fault their system's a piece of crap.
ダサ過ぎんだよこのシステムが
Is there something on my face?
俺の顔に何か付いてるのか
No, there isn't!
いや　別に…
You already get provided with a powerful weapon like the Dominator,
ドミネーターほど強力な武器が支給されるのに
so do you really have to engage in this much combat training?
ここまで過剰な戦闘訓練が必要なんですか
Yeah, I do.
必要だ
Our weapons are powerful, but it's for that very reason
強くて優れた武器を扱うからこそ その使い手はより強くタフでなきゃいけない
that their users have to be even stronger.
In the end, the Dominator doesn't kill people. I do.
相手を殺すのはドミネーターじゃなく この俺だと…
In order to keep that in mind,
それを肝に銘じておくためにも ここにちゃんと痛みを感じておかないとな
I have to feel the pain here.
Are you trying to teach me something?
それって　私に対する教訓ですか
Well, I don't wanna be in a situation
where you have to fire the Dominator.
あんたにドミネーターを撃たせるような状況は 願い下げだぜ
So, what do you want?
で　何の用だ
To start with, please wipe yourself down and put a shirt on!
その前にタオルで汗拭いて服をちゃんと着てください
It's about the unsolved case.
未解決事件
Public Safety Bureau Special Case 102.
公安局 広域重要指定事件１０２について
I looked into it. Sorry to pry into your past.
こっそり　のぞき見するみたいに調べたのは謝ります
What are you apologizing for?
なぜ謝る
You're not angry with me?
怒ってないんですか
Why would I be angry?
どうして俺が怒らなきゃいけないんだ
Because it's an old homicide case that
claimed the life of one of my subordinates?
過去の部下を殺された事件のことで
Because it's been three years and we're
no closer to solving it than when we began?
３年もたつのに解決できてない事件のことで
No reason to be.
怒らないさ
And if I got angry at anyone, it'd be myself.
俺が怒るとすれば
その対象は自分自身以外あり得ない
In that homicide case, I didn't even
come close to finding the mastermind
あの事件　藤間幸三郎の背後で糸を引いていた黒幕に
who'd been pulling the strings behind Touma Kouzaburo.
俺はかすることすらできなかった
Do you think the same guy's behind this case?
今回の事件も同じ人物が関与していると
I don't know yet.
まだ分からない ただの手の込んだだけの模倣犯という可能性もある
It's still possible that this is just an elaborate copycat crime.
But it's definitely worth looking into.
だが　調べる価値があるのは間違いない
You've been taken off the case, though.
捜査から外されちゃいましたね
That's okay.
別にいいさ
I don't wanna cause Gino too much trouble.
あんまりギノを困らせてもな
What?
I'm saying, there's a way to handle these things.
やり方はあるってことだよ
We can find a good pretext to create
a situation where they'd need us back.
うまい口実を見つけて 俺たちが戻らざるを得ない状況を作り出せばいい
Is that really possible?
そんな方法が
It is. Just wait and see.
あるさ　まあ見てろ
What kind of person was Enforcer Sasayama?
佐々山執行官ってどんな人だったんですか
He was a real piece of work.
くそ野郎だった
Huh?
はあ
He was a womanizer.
女好きでね
I lost count of how many times he tried
to grab Karanomori and Kunizuka's butts.
唐之杜や六合塚なんて何度尻を触られたことか
He got slugged every time, but he never seemed to learn his lesson.
そのたびにぶん殴られるのに まったく 懲りる様子がなかったな
He had a short fuse too.
あと短気だった
Once he got upset, there was nothing anyone could do.
一度火が付くと手が付けられなくてな
One day, he went to the house of
a guy who got flagged by a Hue Check.
あるとき 色相チェックに引っ掛かった容疑者宅に踏み込むと
When he stepped inside, this guy was
on top of a woman he had kidnapped.
まさにさらった女性にのしかかってるところだった
Sasayama almost killed the guy.
佐々山はその男を危うく殺しかけた
Since I was an Inspector at the time, I stopped him,
当時俺は監視官だったから 一応止めたが
but deep down, I thought that he was a funny guy.
内心楽しいやつだと思ってた
Yeah. That violent, womanizing bastard was a real funny guy.
女好きで凶暴で 実に楽しいくそ野郎だと…
At the very least, I never expected he'd die that way.
少なくとも　あんな死に方をするような男じゃなかった
Did you see the picture of his body?
死体の写真は見たか
Yes.
はい
We found it underneath a Holographic display.
死体はホログラフ·イルミネーションの裏側に配置されていた
Yes...
はい…
Do you know what kind of display it was?
イルミネーションの内容は知ってるか
No, I don't.
いいえ　そこまでは
It was an ad by a pharmaceutical company.
薬品会社の広告だった
"Our safe stress care will transport you to a world without suffering."
安全なストレスケア 苦しみのない世界へ
Analysis showed that before Sasayama was turned into a specimen,
佐々山は標本化される前
he was dismembered while he was still alive.
生きたまま解体されたことが 分析で判明した
It was like the culprit was sending a message.
犯人のメッセージみたいだったよ
"Life is nothing but suffering."
「苦しいだけが人生だ」って
I wanted the bastard who did that
to Sasayama to meet the same end.
それをしでかしたやつを同じ目に遭わせてやりたいと
Once I started feeling that way,
いつからかそんなふうに思うようになった時点で
my career as an Inspector was over.
監視官としての俺はもう終わってた
Do you have any regrets?
後悔はありませんか
I don't regret my own actions.
自分の行動に後悔はない
But the thing is... the case is still unsolved.
問題は　未解決なこと
That's the only problem.
この一点に尽きる
We need to find the accomplice who
helped Touma Kouzaburo three years ago.
３年前　藤間幸三郎に手を貸した共犯者
Are there any leads that we can still use?
今でも使えそうな手掛かりは 何かありますか
Yeah.
There's a picture that Sasayama took,
佐々山が撮った写真がある
though it's pretty blurry.
ひどくピンぼけだがな
It was saved on the terminal that Sasayama used.
佐々山の使ってた端末に保存されていた
This man? Did you find out what his name was?
この男…名前とかは
The picture's filename was...
画像ファイルのタイトルは…「マキシマ」だった
"Makishima".
They found Kuzuhara Satsuki dead.
死体は葛原沙月さんだった
I heard.
らしいね
Yoshika has been absent from school since yesterday.
葦歌ちゃんが昨日から欠席してる
I heard.
らしいね
Hey, listen to me!
ねえ ちょっと真面目に聞いてよ
I am listening.
聞いてるよ
It's not just Ookubo.
大久保さんだけじゃない Ｂ組の山口昌美も欠席が続いてるってさ
I heard that Yamaguchi Masami in Class B has been absent, too.
Sounds like there's trouble brewing at the Academy.
たぶん　この学園でよくないことが起きている
So?
それで
"So"?
「それで」って
If there's trouble, the first thing you should do is stay out of it.
よくないことには最初から近づかない 噂話もしない
Don't gossip, either.
What are you saying?
何それ…
I feel that careless actions could put us in serious danger.
うかつに動くと 本当に危ない気がする
We've been friends with Yoshika since we were kids, you know.
葦歌ちゃん 私たちの幼なじみじゃない
Ouryou Rikako.
王陵璃華子
Who?
Ookubo was really crazy about her, right?
大久保さん かなり入れ揚げてたんでしょ
And she seemed to be interested in Ookubo as well.
向こうも案外 まんざらでもなかった様子だし
If you ask her, she might know something.
聞いてみたら何か知ってるかもよ
Yeah...
うん…
There's this quote from Kierkegaard that my father liked.
父が好きだったキルケゴールの言葉よ
"Because man is superior to animals,
「人間は動物より勝っているからこそ
in other words, because man is the self, and spirit,
言い換えれば　人間は自己であり精神であるからこそ
man can be in despair."
絶望することができるのである」
Unless you know despair, you cannot know hope.
絶望を知らなければ希望もない
My father used dismembered bodies
as the subject of many of his drawings.
父の絵の題材にバラバラの人体が多いのは
That's because they symbolize the contradictory nature of the self.
自己に抱えた矛盾の象徴なのよ
I had great respect for my father.
私は父を尊敬していた
He was aware of his obligation as an artist
芸術家としての義務を自覚して
and continued to focus intently on
using his creations to enlighten people.
啓蒙としての創作姿勢にこだわり続けたあの人は
I think even now that he was a great artist indeed.
本当に素晴らしい絵描きだったと今でも思ってるわ
That's why I simply can't forgive him
for abandoning that duty halfway through.
だからね　その務めを途中で放棄してしまったことがことさらに許せないの
Yesterday, my father passed away.
昨日ね　父が亡くなったの
He's been as good as dead for a while,
もうとっくに死んだも同然の人だったけど
but finally even his heart gave in.
とうとう心臓まで本当に止まっちゃった
But I'm okay.
でも大丈夫
I'm not sad.
悲しくなんかないわ
I, his daughter, will carry out my father's duty together with you all.
父の務めは　娘の私があなたたちと一緒に果たしていくのよ
Don't you think that's wonderful?
すてきだと思わない？
It's exciting, isn't it,
ドキドキするよね
Yoshika?
葦歌さん
Eustress deficiency cerebral infarction.
ユーストレス欠乏性脳梗塞
Well, that's not the official name for the illness.
まあ 公認の病名ではありません
It is said to be the real cause of most deaths that are declared as
原因不明の心不全という形で処理されている死因のおおかたは
"heart failure from unknown cause".
実は　この症例に該当するといわれています
I've heard of it. They say that it's a side effect of excessive stress care.
聞いたことはある
過度のストレスケアによる弊害だそうだが…
For some time, it's been understood
that moderate stress has beneficial effects.
かねてより適度のストレスは免疫活動を活性化させるなど
For example, it stimulates the immune system.
好ましい効果もあるとされてきた
As they say, it serves as motivation in your life.
いわゆる 人生の張り合い
You could even call it a reason for living.
生きがいと言い直してもいい
However, once Psycho-Pass checks became routine,
ところが　サイコパス診断が恒常化してしまった結果
people have found their sense of stress numbed so heavily that
ストレスの感覚がまひし過ぎて
we started to see patients who
couldn't even recognize stimulation itself.
刺激そのものを認識できなくなる患者が出てきた
Once that happens, they're like living corpses.
こうなると　生ける屍も同然です
Soon their autonomic nervous system stops functioning on its own
やがては自律神経そのものが自らの機能を見失い
and their vital functions shut down.
生命活動を維持できなくなる
That's very sad.
嘆かわしい限りだな
So humans now care for themselves to the point that
人は自らをいたわるあまり
they've actually regressed as living beings, huh?
生物としてはむしろ 退化してしまったわけか
The fact of the matter is,
実はね　これだけ医療体制が発展したにもかかわらず
as much as our medical system has advanced,
statistically, the average lifespan is actually decreasing.
統計上の平均寿命はむしろ 短くなる傾向にあるんですよ
Well, this data will probably never be made public, though.
まあ　決して公にはならないデータでしょうが
That's not surprising.
当然だな
In this era, everything that could be
considered a reason to live has died out.
この時代 生きがいと呼び得るものは全て枯れ果ててしまった
No one tries to talk seriously about what life should be like anymore.
命の在り方を誰も真面目に語ろうとしなくなった
The father of Ouryou Rikako, the girl I mentioned earlier,
くだんの王陵璃華子の父親もね
had eustress deficiency as well.
まさにそのユーストレス欠乏症患者だったんです
Ouryou Rouichi...
王陵牢一
At some point, he was a predominant illustrator.
ある時期一世を風靡したイラストレーターです
Haven't you heard of him?
ご存じありませんか？
Unfortunately, I don't have much knowledge of the art world.
あいにくと美術の世界には造詣がなくてね
He possessed a prodigious talent for drawing
cruel, vivid nightmares using girls' bodies as motifs.
少女の肉体をモチーフに 残虐で生々しい悪夢を描き出す天才でした
However, he himself was a man of quite strict morality.
ところが　本人は至って生真面目なモラリストでね
Well, it's not uncommon for there
to be a disconnect between the creator
まあ　作品のイメージと制作者の実態が乖離しているのは珍しくもない話ですが
and the impression their creations give.
But in Rouichi's case, there was a firm ideology there.
牢一の場合にはそこに確たる理念があった
According to him,
いわく　人間は心の暗部 内に秘めた残虐性を正しく自覚することで
by becoming firmly aware of the cruelty
that hides in the dark depths of the human heart,
humans can foster the common sense, ability to reason,
それを律する良識と理性、善意を培うことができると…
and goodwill to control that cruelty.
He viewed his creative efforts as a means to enlighten the populace.
彼はそのための啓発として自らの創作活動を定義づけていた
From what you say, he sounds like quite the saint.
聞くかぎりではとんだ聖人君主ではないか
However, the spread of Psycho-Pass assessments
しかし　サイコパス判定の普及が彼の自認する役目を終わらせた
ended this role that he had decided for himself.
People don't have to control themselves anymore.
人は自らを律するまでもなく
Instead, they can now maintain their
mental health through machine assessments.
機械による計測で心の健康を保てるようになった
I heard...
牢一はね　このテクノロジーを歓迎したそうです
that Rouichi welcomed this technology.
Whatever the means,
方法はどうあれ 彼が理想とした人の心の健やかなる形は実現した
his ideal of humanity having healthy and sound minds had been realized.
As a result, though, his mission ended and his life lost its meaning.
その結果として自らの使命が完了し
その人生は無価値なものになったわけですが…
I'm surprised.
驚きだな　芸術家などというのは総じて俗物だと思っていたが…
I thought all artists were the same,
concerned only with fame and wealth.
Well, he too probably had inner conflicts.
まあ　心には葛藤もあったでしょうが
But in order to solve them,
牢一はその解消に早速先端技術である各種のストレスケアを活用した
he used all kinds of state-of-the-art stress care methods.
His daughter Rikako tells me that he was so dependent on them
その依存ぶりは耽溺と言っていいほどだったと
that you could call it an addiction.
娘の璃華子は語ってます
As a result,
その結果　ベッドから起き上がることもない 生きた死体に成り果てたと…
he became a living corpse who
couldn't even sit up from his bed, huh?
She loved her father so much that I'm sure
父を慕う娘からしてみれば 許し難い話でしょうね
she couldn't forgive that which took him away.
It's as if Ouryou Rouichi was killed twice.
王陵牢一は二度殺されたようなものです
First, his talent was killed by science and technology.
まずは科学技術によって才能を殺され
And then, his soul was killed by society.
そして社会によって魂を殺された
In short, you mean this girl is
committing crimes to get revenge for her father?
つまり　その少女の犯行の動機は父親の復讐かね？
Well, I don't know.
さて　どうでしょう？
I hope she finds some meaning beyond revenge, though.
願わくば　さらに向こう側の意義を見いだしてほしいものですが…
Choe Gu-Sung?
チェ·グソン？
That was quick.
お早いお出ましで
I do wonder how Mr. Makishima knew that
there was a place like this inside the Academy.
それにしても槙島先生はどうして学園内にこんな場所があるなんて知っていたのかしら？
It seems this used to be a generator
room that powered a recycling boiler,
もともとはリサイクルボイラーの発電室だったのが
but when the Academy was
renovated, it disappeared from the blueprints.
改装で閉鎖されたとき 図面からも抜け落ちたみたいで
How slipshod, huh?
ずさんなもんです
So where are the chemicals?
それで　薬の方は？
Over there.
そちらに
Deliveries aren't usually my thing,
別に俺の専門は荷運びじゃないんですがね
but the payment this time is quite generous.
今回は手当も弾んでもらえてますし
Not to mention I get to help out a cute young lady like yourself.
こんなカワイイお嬢さんのお手伝いってんなら
So, I hardly have reason to complain.
まあ　文句をつける筋合いでもありませんな
Where does Mr. Makishima get weird stuff like this?
こんな不思議なものを 槙島先生はいったいどこから？
He did mention that they were leftover stockpiles from past festivities.
昔仕込んだ祭りの残りとは言ってましたがね
I don't know who made it.
誰が作ったもんなのかは知らないし 知りたくもないが
I don't even want to.
The person must've thought that entertaining Makishima would be a lot more worthwhile
そいつはこの妙ちきりんな薬で特許取ったり商いをしたりするより
than getting a patent for this weird chemical or selling it.
槙島の旦那を楽しませる方がよほど有意義だと思ったんでしょうね
He does seem to attract geniuses that have gone astray.
先生の周囲にはいつも才能の使いどころを間違えた天才が集まってくるのでしょうね
And you're one of them, right, Choe Gu-Sung?
あなたもその１人なのでしょう？
チェ·グソン…
I don't know what it is,
何なんですかね～
but when I'm with him, I feel like
I'm reliving my childhood or something.
あの人と一緒にいると 童心に帰るっていうか
I start to wonder what mischief we
should get up to in order to shake up society,
どんないたずらを仕掛けて世間をあっと言わせてやるか
and my thoughts become consumed with those ideas.
そればっかり夢中になっちまう
I know the feeling.
分かるわ　その気持ち
You guys prepare toys,
あなたたちがおもちゃを用意し
and we, mischievous children that
we are, use those toys to create a stir.
それを使って私たちのようないたずらっ子が世の中を騒がせる
It really is fun, isn't it?
楽しいわよね 本当に
Well, us toy manufacturers
まあ　俺らおもちゃ屋は
have enough fun just watching what you brats do next.
あんたたち悪がきのやることを眺めて楽しむだけで十分です
Yeah. I'd say they're probably
discovering my second prank right about now.
そうね そろそろ２つ目のいたずらが見つかる頃合いじゃないかしら
Keep an eye on the news.
ニュースに注目しとくといいわ
Will do.
そうさせてもらいましょう
You always leave before the really fun stuff begins.
あなた いつも一番楽しい場面には付き合わずに帰っちゃうのね
It's a shame you miss it.
もったいないわ
Unfortunately, I don't do too well around blood and stuff, so I'll pass.
あいにく 血なまぐさいのは苦手なもんでね
A second one...
２件目か…
If this is really Touma Kouzaburo's doing, that makes it the sixth.
これが藤間幸三郎の犯行なら ６件目ですよ
So, what was it that you wanted to ask me, Kawarazaki Kagami?
それで私に相談事って何かしら？
川原崎加賀美さん
It's Yoshika...
葦歌ちゃん…
It's about Ookubo.
大久保さんの件なんです
She's been absent from school for
the last three days in a row, so... um...
彼女もう３日続けて欠席してて その…
So you're worried. You care about your friends.
心配なのね 川原崎さんは友達思いね
We've been friends since we were kids.
彼女 私の幼なじみで…
What's this?
これは…
Friendship between girls is wonderful, isn't it?
女の子同士の友情ってすてきね
I think it might end up being a very exciting motif.
それはそれでモチーフとしてとっても刺激的かも
Um...
It might also be a good addition to
my Yoshika exhibition, don't you think?
葦歌さんを展示するに当たって
そういう志向もいいわよね
A touching reunion with your childhood friend.
幼なじみとの感動の対面
It's an emotionally stirring scene, isn't it?
心揺さぶられる場面よね
It really makes me cry.
本当　泣かせられるわ
I want to reenact this moving scene in
a place where more and more people can see it.
この感動をもっともっと大勢の目に付くところで再現したいってそう思ってしまうのが
Perhaps it really is the fate of artists to be struck by such inspiration.
やはり表現者の業かしらね
Fearii teeru wa
It seems all fairy tales
Sakki shinda mitai
Are dead
Renga no byoutou de
In a hospital ward of brick stones
Umaku utaenakute
My voice is too coarse to sing
Kiri ni kemuru yoru
Outside in the foggy haze
Ukabe akai tsuki
A red moon glows
Hora mite watashi wo
Look at me
Me wo sorasanai de
Do not avert your gaze
Kuroi tetsu goushi no naka de
Behind black bars
Watashi wa umarete kitanda
I was born
Behind black bars
Kuroi tetsu goushi no naka de
I was born
Watashi wa umarete kitanda
Akui no daishou wo negae
I wish there were a punishment for evil
I was born
Watashi wa umarete kitanda
I wish there were a punishment for evil
Akui no daishou wo negae
Nozomu ga mama ni omae ni
Always I need you
I wish there were a punishment for evil
Akui no daishou wo negae
Always I need you
Nozomu ga mama ni omae ni
Saa ataeyou seigi wo
Now, grant us justice
Always I need you
Nozomu ga mama ni omae ni
Now, grant us justice
Saa ataeyou seigi wo
Kowashite kowasareru mae ni
Before chaos takes us all
Now, grant us justice
Saa ataeyou seigi wo
Before chaos takes us all
Kowashite kowasareru mae ni
Inga no daishou wo harai tomo ni yukou
Pay the price of fate and let us go together,
Before chaos takes us all
Kowashite kowasareru mae ni
Pay the price of fate and let us go together,
Inga no daishou wo harai tomo ni yukou
Namae no nai kaibutsu
Nameless beasts
Pay the price of fate and let us go together,
Inga no daishou wo harai tomo ni yukou
Nameless beasts
Namae no nai kaibutsu
This story is a work of fiction. The names of all individuals and organizations that appear
in this show are fictitious and any similarity to those in existence in the real world is purely coincidental.
This is a world where the mental state and
personal tendencies of humans can be quantified.
While all sorts of inclinations are recorded and policed,
these measured numbers used to judge people's souls are
commonly called "Psycho-Pass".
This is a world where the mental state and
personal tendencies of humans can be quantified.
While all sorts of inclinations are recorded and policed,
these measured numbers used to judge people's souls are
commonly called "Psycho-Pass".